Rothstein, Richard Collection of ACWA-ACTWU Files 6142
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Richard Rothstein Collection of ACWA-ACTWU Files
1955-1989
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Rothstein, Richard
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America
6142
26.89 cubic feet
26.9 linear ft.
Posters.
5819041
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 06, 2002
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records
Clothing workers -- Labor unions-- United States -- Posters; Textile workers -- Labor unions--United States -- Posters; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union
5819041
- Made in USA- TV Program (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Newsletters from ACTWU and ILGWU (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Sachen Moving (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Misc. Moving Grievance (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Contracts- Other Areas, #1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Contracts- Other Areas, #2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Brown Shoe (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Election Results- ACTWU (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Xerox- Comparative Benefits (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Area Contracts- Other Unions (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ACTWU Electronics Contracts (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Organizing Leaflets (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ACTWU Election Reports (Box 1, Folder 14)
- L.A.D.O.C. (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Stevens Campaign - Rock Hill #1, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Stevens Campaign - Rock Hill #2, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Stevens Campaign - Rock Hill #3, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- California Corporations (Box 1, Folder 19)
- EOS Subcontractors (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Hayward Org. Committee (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Fresno Organizing (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Orange County Organizing (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Sacramento Area (Box 1, Folder 24)
- San Diego Organizing Committee (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Santa Monica Union Organizing (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Organizing Leaflets (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Leaflet Samples AFL-CIO (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Leaflet Samples Amalgamated Clothing (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Zimmerman, Galanty, and Fiman- Letterhead and Envelopes (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Union Busters (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Union Campaign Activities- Management (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Management Anti-Union Campaigns (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Company Campaign- GERICO and Western Arts (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Consultants (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Misc. Anti-Union Propaganda (Box 2, Folder 11)
- ACTWU CB Cases (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Stevens' Negative Propaganda (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Farah (Box 2, Folder 14)
- J. P. Stevens Misc. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence 1
- J. P. Stevens Misc. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Correspondence 2
- J. P. Stevens Misc. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Correspondence 3
- J. P. Stevens Misc. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Correspondence 4
- J. P. Stevens Misc. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Correspondence 5
- J. P. Stevens Misc. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Correspondence 6
- J. P. Stevens Misc. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Correspondence 7
- J. P. Stevens Misc. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Correspondence 8
- ACTWU, CA Joint Board vs. Kauffman's Enterprises (Box 3, Folder 1)
- A Brief History of the Amalgamated (Box 3, Folder 2)
- A Workers Guide to Contract Language, Action Newsletter, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Spring 1984-Winter 1984, Spring, Winter 1985, Autumn, Winter 1986
- TWUA Leadership Manual- COPE and Education Departments (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Conference on Project Counter-Attack (Box 3, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Regional Conferences, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Briar Inc. vs. The California Joint Board (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Unions in North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Pacific Columbia Mills (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Erwin Mills (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Cranston Print Works Company (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Fieldcrest Mills Inc. (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Colorado Joint Board- Constitution and by-laws (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Xerox- Employee Assistance Program (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Performance Teams- Xerox (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Agreement Between J.P. Stevens and ACTWU 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Agreement Between J.P. Stevens and ACTWU 2 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Agreement Between Xerox and Xerographic Division, ACTWU 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Agreement Between Xerox and Xerographic Division, ACTWU 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Agreements Reached Between Xerox Corporation and ACTWU (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Collective Bargaining Proposals of the ACTWU on Behalf of the California Joint Board and its Local 1414c, Presented to Xerox Corp.-Diablo Systems Inc.- 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Collective Bargaining Proposals of the ACTWU on Behalf of the California Joint Board and its Local 1414c, Presented to Xerox Corp.-Diablo Systems Inc.- 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Agreement Between Xerographic Division and Xerox Corp. 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Agreement Between Xerographic Division and Xerox Corp. 2 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Agreement Between Xerox (Pomona Printed Wiring Boards Plant) and the ACTWU 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Agreement Between Xerox (Pomona Printed Wiring Boards Plant) and the ACTWU 2 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- California Joint Board vs. Chase Bag Company 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- California Joint Board vs. Chase Bag Company 2 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Ben Kluger & Associates vs. California Joint Board (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Ben Kluger & Associates vs. California Joint Board 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Ben Kluger & Associates vs. California Joint Board 2 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- EOS Sale (Box 4, Folder 12)
- EOS Negotiations 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- EOS Negotiations 2 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Hall Committee (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Pre-Retirement Counseling/Grants/ Muscular Dystrophy (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Grants etc. (Box 4, Folder 17)
- X.E.A.P (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Solicitation and Distribution Rules (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Zimmerman (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Thompson (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Neal de Snow (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Jamie Rodriguez (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Speeches (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Campaign for Joint Board Manager (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Joint Board Staff Manager (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Elease Foster Grievance (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Diablo Negotiations, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Mary Anne Thorin (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Agreements Between Xerox Corp. and ACTWU (Box 4, Folder 30)
- EOS ETA 39-82 (Larry Brown) (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Misc. Joint Board Correspondence, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- L.A. Joint Board (Box 5, Folder 3)
- F.O.U.R. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Dues Problems (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Model Constitution (Box 5, Folder 6)
- ACTWU-PAC (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Joint Board Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 8)
- National Per Capita (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Proposed Merger (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Organizing Reports (Box 5, Folder 11)
- West Coast Regional Joint Board (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Monterrey Mills (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Krochs/Schuessler (Box 5, Folder 14)
- RHV Crystal Lake (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Roanoke Rapids (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Steel Contract (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Ray Rogers and J.P. Stevens Co. (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Kayser Roth Research (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Roanoke Rapids Proposals 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Roanoke Rapids Proposals 2 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Industrial Rock Hill (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Rock Hill- Industrial 1 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Rock Hill- Industrial 2 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- West Boylston (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Primary Target- JPS (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Campaign Summary (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Settlement Possibilities 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Settlement Possibilities 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Kaiser-Roth Allendale (Box 6, Folder 5)
- High Point Misc. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- High Point- Post Election Activity (Box 6, Folder 7)
- High Point Union Leaflets (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Letter to Potential Union Members from J. P. Stevens (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Affidavits (Box 6, Folder 10)
- High Point 11-CA-8836 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- High Point 11-RC-4749 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- High Point and Anti-Union Committee Leaflets (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Allendale Company and Committee Anti-Union Leaflets (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Allendale Post-election Activity (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Allendale RR Notes (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Allendale Business Community Anti-Union Activity (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Allendale 1 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Allendale 2 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Allendale Union Leaflets (Box 6, Folder 20)
- ULP Affidavits Allendale (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Allendale RC-4765 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Allendale ULPs (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Union Leaflets Tifton (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Tifton Campaign (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Tifton 10-RC-11933 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Diablo Larry Jordan 81-22 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- 81-2 (Diablo) Mike Manley (Box 7, Folder 6)
- 80-111 Walt Hemming (Diablo) (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Time Limits and Arbitrability (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Stipulations (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Exhibits (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Rejected Stipulations (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Hirsch Memoranda (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Pending Arbitrations- Arrangements (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Notes for Preparation- Troxler 1 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Notes for Preparation- Troxler 2 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Labor Organizations in Wyoming and Manufacturers in Utah (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Gerico (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Gerico Election Campaign (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Alpine Designs (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Agreement Between Gerico and the Chicago Joint Board (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Gerico, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  9/15-9/16/76
- Grievance Procedures/Notes/Agreements (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Articles of Agreement- Gerico Co. (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Gerico- Economic Proposals (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Prior Co. (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Prior Negotiations (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Prior Company- Agreements and Notes (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Prior Company 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Prior Company 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Ann Lee 1110 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Ann Lee Sportswear II (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Antonelli, Ind. (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Current Campaign Chicago Com. 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Current Campaign Chicago Com. 2 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Checks and Receipts (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Notes/Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Alpine Knitting Negotiations, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Antonelli Industries Strike 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Antonelli Industries Strike 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Blue Mt. Arts- Organizing and Negotiation (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Bonds- JTU 3 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Champion Glove- Des Moines (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Daire (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Frostline, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Gerico III (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Gerico Card Verification (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Antonelli Negotiations (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Atlantis Wax (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Au'Buchon 27-CA-5050 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Au'Buchon (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Alpine Knitting Mills (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Bayly Pleasant Grove 866 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Bayly Greeley (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Leaflets Past Campaigns (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Leaflets Past Campaigns (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Haggar San Antonio (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Head Organizing Campaign 1 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Head Organizing Campaign 2 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Ann Lee Sportswear I (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Ann Lee Sportswear I (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Gerry (Denver) Negotiations (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Holloway Sportswear, Jackson Center, Ohio (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Holubar (Box 10, Folder 5)
- J.H.B Imports (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Lovett (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Mack Johns (Box 10, Folder 8)
- O'Bryan Bros. Iowa (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Colonial Life Insurance- The Prior Company (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Risto "C" Case (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Steiner (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Western Arts, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Current Campaign Corr-Notes/Loevy 1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Current Campaign Corr-Notes/Loevy 2 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Company Campaign- Prior (Lerten) (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Gerico/Western Arts Company Campaign (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Bills and Receipts (Box 10, Folder 18)
- ACTWU Bank Statements- Wells Fargo Bank (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Contract for Local 122, Shoe Division (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Delegates (Box 10, Folder 21)
- ACTWU Members for a Better Union (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Nicholas (Box 10, Folder 23)
- California Joint Board, Immigration (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Jack Sheinkman (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Joint Board Constitution (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Private Meeting (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Per Capita/Wage Survey (Box 10, Folder 28)
- L.U. Ballots, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Merger (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Meeting Minutes (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Temple Inc. (Box 11, Folder 3)
- F.O.U.R. Negotiations (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Staff Meetings (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Finances (Box 11, Folder 6)
- LM2 Form (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Business Agent Elections, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Northern California Joint Board (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Addresses of Members (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Monthly Membership Figures (Box 11, Folder 11)
- ACTWU Elections, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Amoco Fabrics vs. ACTWU (Box 11, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens and Company vs. ACTWU (Box 11, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens and Company vs. ACTWU (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Kayser-Roth, Allendale Division vs. ACTWU (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Agreement Between the Xerox Company and the Xerographic Division (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Sample Leaflets (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Sample Leaflets (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Nuclear Freeze Campaign (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Nuclear Freeze Campaign (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Labor Committee/Weapons Freeze (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Labor Committee/Weapons Freeze (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Denver Area Labor Federation- AFL-CIO 1 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Denver Area Labor Federation- AFL-CIO 2 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Duty to Supply Information/Strategic Organizing (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Incentive Systems (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Job Slotting (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Stewards Manuals (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Stewards Manuals (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Stewards Training- Individual Sheets (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Stewards Case Studies- Grievances (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Strike Manuals (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Post Election Strategy (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Correspondence Folder 1, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Correspondence Folder 2, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Correspondence Folder 3, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Correspondence Folder 1 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Correspondence Folder 2 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Correspondence Folder 3 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Apparel Industry Production (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Kayser-Roth 11-RC-4975 and 11-CA (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Photos (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Report of the General Executive Board, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Bayly Provo (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Bernard's JTU3 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Blue Mountain Arts (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Brigham Apparel (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Fashion Bar J.T.U. 3 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Gano Dowws- Local 3 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Stuart Fitzpatrick NOG, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Local 3 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- May D+F (Box 13, Folder 7)
- PPWE Lander, WYO (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Whitco Col. Sp. 1 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Whitco 2 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Zohn- Local 263 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Shops to Check Out 1 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Shops to Check Out 2 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- AMF Head (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Aspen Skiwear- Pueblo, Denver, Lamar (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Frostline (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Down Products (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Kayline (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Sugarhouse Awning (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Placement Issues (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Receipt Books (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Diablo 82-83 (Transducers) (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Insurance Relating to Amalgamated (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Agreement Between Loral Electro Optical Systems Inc. and Local 1414F (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Agreement Between Xerox Corp. and ACTWU (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Receipts, Constitution, Fourth Steps (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Address Cards (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Campaign Leaflets and Union Propaganda (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Kayser-Roth- Leaflets, Co and U (Box 14, Folder 2)
- "Inhuman Relations" Guillermo Grenier Folder 1 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- "Inhuman Relations" Guillermo Grenier Folder 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Employer Material Used in TWUA Organizing Campaigns 1 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Employer Material Used in TWUA Organizing Campaigns 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Proposed Agreement Between J.P. Stevens and ACTWU (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Training (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Staff Mailings, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens vs. ACTWU (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Sadlowski (Box 14, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens, Allendale, and General Dynamics (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Union Bulletin Boards and other Information (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Workers Unity Org. (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Stevens Corporate Campaign (Box 14, Folder 15)
- MWA Labor Seminar (Box 14, Folder 16)
- National Organizing Structure Committee (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Organizing American Labor (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Organizing Crystal Zoo (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Notes and Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Statistical Information and Other Repots and Papers (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Magazine Articles and Photocopied Newspaper Clippings (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Newspaper Clippings (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Gerico, Gerry, and Prior (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Leaflets, Misc (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Leaflets- ACWA (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Midwest Academy (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Late 1970's
- Leaflets- I.U.D. (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Zody's Ceres 32-CB-1363 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- San Francisco Office (Box 15, Folder 11)
- S.U.B. Program (Chicago) (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Workman's Comp and Oc. Dis. Dis. Act., Minimum Wage and Unemployment Compensation (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Misc. Memos from Chicago (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Federal Register- Occupational Health and Safety Standards (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Health/Safety COSHA/OSHA (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Regional Structure (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Staff Notes (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Organizer's Training (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Insurance (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Joe Albert's Store (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Alpine Designs 1123 Folder 1 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Alpine Designs 1123 Folder 2 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- American Linen Ogden (Box 15, Folder 24)
- American Linen Salt Lake 562 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Camp 7 Folder 1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Camp 7 Folder 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Denver Dry (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Gerico Inc (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Gerico 1156 Folder 1 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Gerico 1156 Folder 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Gerico Averages (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Pioneer Wear (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Tucumcari Apparel (Box 16, Folder 9)
- D.S.O.C (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Mountain States Employer's Council (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Korea (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Multi-Nationals (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Politics, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- CDFP (Box 16, Folder 15)
- N.L.R.B. (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Labor Law Folder 1 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Labor Law Folder 2 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Contract Expirations (Box 16, Folder 19)
- California Joint Board Meeting Minutes (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Ethicon J+J Folder 1 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Ethicon J+J Folder 2 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Ethicon J+J Folder 3 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Ethicon J+J Folder 4 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Ethicon J+J Folder 5 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Ethicon J+J Folder 6 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Misc. (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Bag and Packaging Industry (Box 17, Folder 2)
- California Joint Board: Elections and Controversy 1 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- California Joint Board: Elections and Controversy 2 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Labor Unity Newspaper September and October, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Notes (Box 17, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens (Box 17, Folder 7)
- L.A. Joint Board Audit Report (Box 17, Folder 8)
- National Weapon Freeze Staff Search (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Fechheimer 1110 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Hirsch-Tyler and Fechheimer I 1110 Folder 1 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Hirsch-Tyler and Fechheimer I 1110 Folder 2 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Articles on Camp 7/Court of Appeals Decision/Head Leaflets (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Staff Guidelines/Joint Board Representatives (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Action Complementary List (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Interviews that Need to be Scheduled (Box 17, Folder 16)
- ACTWU Members for a Better Union (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Joint Board and Local Officers (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Organizers Meeting (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Amnesty (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Contract Proposals/Committees (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Article Ideas for the Next Issue of Action (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Dues Card Messages (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Financial Information (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Individual Member Local (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Joint Board Planning (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Community Support (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Joint Board Financial Planning Staff Assignments 1 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Joint Board Financial Planning Staff Assignments 2 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Org. Dir. Search (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Gerry Alamosa (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Gerry Scottsbluff 2284 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Tucumcaui Ind. 2nd Election Campaign (Box 17, Folder 33)
  Co-Leaflets, Union Leaflets, Objections to Both Elections and Letters
- Union Membership Cards (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Head NLRB 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Head NLRB 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Head Ski Company Folder 1 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Head Ski Company Folder 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Head Injunction (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Mead Ski- Health and Safety (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Replacements and Strikers- Head Ski (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Contract Suggestions for the Head Ski Company (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Articles of Agreement for Head Ski Company (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Vachon Comp Case- Mahoney Comp Case (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Head Post Election II (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Head IV (Excluded from Subpoena) Folder 1 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Head IV (Excluded from Subpoena) Folder 2 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Head IV (Excluded from Subpoena) Folder 3 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Gerry Outdoor Sports I (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Gerry II Folder 1 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Gerry II Folder 2 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Head Contract Demands (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Colorado Union Information and Agreements (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Surveys, Temporaries Information, Statements, and Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Head Ski vs. Midwest Regional Joint Board (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Clarks Directory of Southern Textile Mills, Special Convention of ACTWU, Proceedings of the 19th Biennial Convention- TWUA (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Workloads Language (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Wage Negotiations-Data (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Stevens Workloads Negotiations (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Cecil Adkins Grievance- Stevens (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Stevens Shop Negotiations (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Gerry- Denver 1171 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Risto Folder 1 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Risto Folder 2 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Misc Stevens (Box 19, Folder 11)
- "They Said it Couldn't be Done," "The Hollow Promise," "Conspiracy in Southern Textiles," "...almost believable" (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Union Organizing, Decertifying, and Disorganizing (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Organizing Information (Box 19, Folder 14)
- "The Organizing Campaign" (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Textile Hi*lights, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  March, June, September, November, and December 1988 January- March 1989
- "Comparative Survey of Major Collective Bargaining Agreements" (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Report of the General Executive Board, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- "The US Textile and Apparel Industry: A Revolution in Progress" (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Photocopies of Magazine Articles and Papers: Made in the USA and Free Trade (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Magazine Articles and Papers: Made in the USA (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Magazine Articles and Papers (Box 20, Folder 1)
- EPI Proposal (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Apparel, EPI Report Correspondence and Working Notes Folder 1 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Apparel, EPI Report Correspondence and Working Notes Folder 2 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Economic Policy Institute Report on the US Apparel Manufacturing Industry (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Comments on Draft (Box 20, Folder 6)
- MIT Commission on Industrial Productivity (Box 20, Folder 7)
- The Use and Economic Impact of TSUS Items 806.30 and 807.00 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- MIT Early Draft (Box 20, Folder 9)